<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><contentList>
	<content contentuid="hfaa9495bgf4b2g4e9egb8a4g76ce3114f1e2" version="1">Graz'zt's Box of Pleasure</content>
	<content contentuid="hbd7dbcfage396g4a04gaf80g0e1cbef1b923" version="1">An exquisite box that when held close whispers in your ears of pleasures unimaginable within. Dare you indulge yourself?</content>


	<content contentuid="h006cdbccgb99dg41dag88c8gaa169f365660" version="1">Ring of Graz'zt</content>
	<content contentuid="hf332a893gb7e5g48e8ga172gb1350ba26258" version="1">This exquisite ring boasts multiple faceted edges. Surprisingly, wearing such a sharp design, instead of inducing discomfort, evokes a sense of captivating pleasure.</content>

	<content contentuid="hb53111fdg2a06g4db0ga18ag955f373b88ea" version="1">Rings of Graz'zt</content>
	<content contentuid="h1a8869deg6af7g4288gabb6g51a44e4dac4f" version="1">Warped under the Dark Prince's influence and your submission to pleasure, the once benign ring shifted from your finger to embed itself into your nipples. Forged from the Abyss's darkest materials, they bear intricate markings, a phantom echo of a dread promise inscribed by Graz'zt himself. Wearing these rings is not simply an accessorizing choice, but a profound declaration of submission to Graz'zt's will. They look very painful to remove.</content>

	<content contentuid="hf2880447g4608g455fg8f53gb17e9f991973" version="1">Chains of Graz'zt</content>
	<content contentuid="h650c93fbg1a38g416dg9c78g55040bd051c8" version="1">Warped under the Dark Prince's influence and your submission to pleasure, the once benign ring shifted from your finger to embed itself into your nipples. Forged from the Abyss's darkest materials, they bear intricate markings, a phantom echo of a dread promise inscribed by Graz'zt himself. Chains bind them together, each link carrying the weight of your depravity. Wearing these signals your profound dedication to the Dark Prince himself..</content>

	<content contentuid="hde2acefage3dfg4bb7g9be1g168e5a850419" version="1">Chains of Submission</content>
	<content contentuid="hd8054508gd245g4f57ga37fgd0b797b5f41f" version="1">Warped further by the Dark Prince's influence and your unabashed surrender to pleasure, the Chains of Graz'zt transformed yet again. Adapting to your deepening depravity, a third piercing emerges to mark your most intimate area, binding it by chain to the existing links. Crafted from the Abyss's darkest materials, each piece bears intricate markings. It is a tangible symbol of your hedonistic ascension. Transcending beyond Graz'zt, it marks your dedication to the concept of Submission itself. </content>


	<content contentuid="hc9532287gc215g4b64gb0b9gdcf1c6b88168" version="1">Hide Piercings</content>
	<content contentuid="h1d34609fg9056g40f0g8b16g75d78b3f0719" version="1">Project a deceptive illusion to conceal the piercings. Although they remain unseen by others, the sensation of their existence is accentuated with every gesture you make.</content>

	<content contentuid="h141bfe18g45c2g41adga510gb4940086a823" version="1">Stop Hiding Piercings</content>
	<content contentuid="h8663aa4ag1880g401fg8dfegedccb4cfbab7" version="1">Unveil the piercings, allowing others to see the source of your squirming.</content>

	<content contentuid="hd8b60198g3295g4492g8c2bg6573aa4d468c" version="1">Hide Lust Brand</content>
	<content contentuid="hf6bbaac1g667fg4ed8g9991gf530b010e6cc" version="1">Suppress your lust brand from showing. While it remains hidden to others, their influence is felt by how it twists any innocent thoughts into indulgent ones.</content>

	<content contentuid="hf59a353ag7163g4c58g9a71gc292983f66df" version="1">Stop Hiding Lust Brand</content>
	<content contentuid="h55831fcege9d0g417ega07fga644c2be1514" version="1">Unveil your Lust Brand, displaying your lustful nature.</content>


	<content contentuid="hbcb5e2e9g3071g45ccg9c2ag542923c2bfb5" version="1">Dark Inspection</content>
	<content contentuid="h8f9aedb4gc403g4826g85f6g1464f6ffae21" version="1">You channel your new profane powers to peer into someone's dark history.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Report the target's Max Pleasure, the number of Bliss they've experienced, and the Bliss they've caused others.</content>


	<content contentuid="hd7a5e852g115fg4acag9d5cg434b0db1cf45" version="1">Touch of Graz'zt</content>
	<content contentuid="h0d74cf45g725dg491fgad60g66d042395078" version="1">Caress of Graz'zt</content>
	<content contentuid="h80a730ddg41f6g4c3eg9de5gaac90824d9e7" version="1">Embrace of Graz'zt</content>
	<content contentuid="h78ae2f4bg1e76g4211g81d4gc2868ea95615" version="1">Surrender yourself to spectral caresses, letting ethereal hands explore your body. You gain [1] + &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityModifier"&gt;Charisma Modifier&lt;/LSTag&gt; and receive [2] &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="LI_PLEASURE"&gt;Pleasure&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>

	<content contentuid="hf788275agceb2g4d5fga7a4g420bf51538a6" version="1">Lust Brand</content> 
	<content contentuid="h8142038fg3a37g4debga007g8a0224322227" version="1">Imbued with dark potency, this indelible mark stirs unnatural desire in any that gaze upon it. Skillfully etched into your womb, the Lust Brand is a constant reminder that you are undeniably a creature of pure, untempered lust. It impairs your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Wisdom"&gt;Wisdom&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Intelligence"&gt;Intelligence&lt;/LSTag&gt; by [1] while boosting your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Charisma"&gt;Charisma&lt;/LSTag&gt; by the same amount.</content>  

	<content contentuid="hc65a1066gd4dcg4c8fga47cg0663c71c35a9" version="1">Ecstatic Lash</content>
	<content contentuid="hc806e45dg9782g457fg9458g139fbfeb3ce0" version="2">Concentrate your hedonistic thoughts into an ethereal whip, striking at the minds of your foes. You inflict [3] + &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityModifier"&gt;Charisma Modifier&lt;/LSTag&gt; &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="LI_PLEASURE"&gt;Pleasure&lt;/LSTag&gt;; if they are in &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="LI_BLISS"&gt;Bliss&lt;/LSTag&gt;, their mind is overwhelmed and they suffer damage. Otherwise, they gain [2] and move [1] towards you, seeking the source of their pleasure.</content>

	<content contentuid="h168d0c0dg168cg47f0g8bffg96a6dad6bca4" version="1">Lustful High</content>
	<content contentuid="h12913d1ag170eg4c7cg9702g98261303a6a1" version="2">Your arousal distracts you from pain, letting you endure more than usual and providing you [1].</content>


	<content contentuid="h21177641gd1cdg4273g8986g9addca845dcf" version="1">After a breathlessly wet dream, you wake to find the Ring of Graz'zt gone from your finger. You panic until you feel a slightly painful burning in your chest, and you realize the ring has split in two and embedded itself in your nipples. Graz'zt has claimed you in your sleep, and you are His.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each transformed ring bears a sinister black sheen, its surface eerily smooth against your skin. Spiked adornments, reminiscent of thorns on a rose stem, trace along its length, hinting at a painful removal. His claim is not easily relinquished. </content> 
	<content contentuid="h2d77b445ga917g493cga3b1g3e2c07e01b14" version="1">After succumbing to pleasure again, you realize with a start that something is off this time. Usually, the pleasure builds to a peak then ebbs, but the wave you're currently riding on seems to continue to build. Your hands follow that feeling, almost of their own accord, but stop a few inches short: there's a heat, a throbbing warmth that wasn't there before. You glance down and your breath catches. A mark, a brand- His brand! now claims your pubic mound, glowing with a pink light that pulses in time with your breath. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As your hands begin downward once more and your eyes close, the last thing you see before succumbing to pleasure is the brand's glow, beating in time with your ragged, hungry breaths.</content> 
	<content contentuid="h685322a8gf4e4g42b2g8adeg01a6838bd05a" version="1">You feel a sinister gaze in your sleep. Fortunately for you, or unfortunately, Graz'zt seems to already have his eyes set on another in your party. He spares you only a glance, and the rest of your dream is a sweet and incoherent mess. (remove the ring when sleeping to avoid this message)</content> 

	<content contentuid="hb3436a69g5fe9g47d8g8bdcg1f6c577d38a5" version="1">, Consort of Graz'zt</content> 

	<content contentuid="h4eb20687g805cg44e2gbd44g0f27a1396731" version="1">Abyssal Inheritance: Soul Branding</content> 
	<content contentuid="h77039ab3g086fg4419g874cgada38d554dc1" version="1">Through experience, you have come to better understand how to give others Bliss. This is when they are most vulernable, and something urges you to leave your mark on them, devouring their potential for your own.</content>  

	<content contentuid="hfba2dee3g02a6g4324gbd9bgdca9e9642f7d" version="1">Soul Brand</content> 
	<content contentuid="he8567035g78b1g4c1bgbe03ga35dc08ae331" version="1">You exploit someone's vulnerability when in &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="LI_BLISS"&gt;Bliss&lt;/LSTag&gt; to permanently mark their soul, devouring their potential for your own. Their resistance will get weaker the more they are overloaded by Bliss.</content>  

	<content contentuid="h9bf02c9bgf7ddg44ceg8e1eg023f96d55bd5" version="1">Soul Branding Fatigue</content> 
	<content contentuid="hc8831433g9237g4fe3g8701g3fe378a8e671" version="1">Soul branding is not to be done lightly. You are exhausted, body and soul, from attempting to do so. You suffer -1 to Charisma and Constitution per stack. You lose 1 stack per turn.</content>  

	<content contentuid="haecf5a8cg9f44g4169g861fgcebc4b56e2d9" version="1">Power consuming</content> 
	<content contentuid="h322a959egaf76g4f72gbc10g8d52412babcc" version="1">The newly formed soul brand is transferring power from the target to you.</content>  
	<content contentuid="h7336905dgccc5g4e6bgac44ge03766a7385e" version="1">Power draining</content> 
	<content contentuid="h53b9b7acgea92g4df1g915cg628572698478" version="1">Your power is being quickly drained away.</content>  

	<content contentuid="h9a5242a6ge625g473cg9f4bgac57cf0d5dd7" version="1">Soul Brand (no Bliss Overload)</content> 
	<content contentuid="h03c55beeg8904g47bbga761gc67aeaa65cdc" version="1">Soul Brand (Bliss Overload I)</content> 
	<content contentuid="h963fa96bg9878g43d1gb638gc0e4ef043b54" version="1">Soul Brand (Bliss Overload II)</content> 
	<content contentuid="hb80e2c4bgd14bg4d30ga755g2dd3872bb5ff" version="1">Soul Brand (Bliss Overload III)</content> 
	<content contentuid="hebae3f16g5cc6g4e66gb6f3g341f7e74ffca" version="1">Soul Brand (Bliss Overload IV)</content> 
	<content contentuid="hfa29d6c9ge521g4597ga948g4611c53311cf" version="1">Soul Brand (Bliss Overload V)</content> 

	<content contentuid="ha709ac40g498bg4b91g9f8egf03100a9d2e4" version="1">As you bring yet another person to Bliss, you feel a connection to some long forgotten instinct, as if experiencing a new taste for the first time. Dark whispers urges you to take advantage of their vulnerability from Bliss to steal their strength for your own.</content> 

	<content contentuid="h33ad0a3bg1356g4f1cgbe4bgec353d03193b" version="1">As the brand burns upon Karlach's soul, power courses through you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Lust. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; The strength that runs through Karlach, the strength that once felled devils and demons, begins to flow out of her, passing through your connection and into your body.  You feel yourself swell with power, a burning heat coursing through you for but an instant as hot power pours into you.  Muscles, svelte and lithe, now adorn your perfected frame, a subtle strength underpinning your generous curves. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; At the same time, you watch Karlach soften in body and mind, her battle-hardened warrior's form melting away, her form growing plush and soft, weak and helpless.  As she gasps and pants herself back to consciousness, you see that the dazed look of her climax shall never truly leave her, her mind now forever clouded, if only slightly, in a haze of pleasure and contentment.</content>
 	<content contentuid="h8b87ca62g354ag4d00g84e9g6bfec12d30da" version="1">Soul Branded: Karlach</content> 
	<content contentuid="h85488343g6841g462ega04cgdaf5ec52d302" version="1">Karlach has been marked as a concubine of Grazzt. Her strength has been stolen, and the inferno that once raged is now but a comforting heat on lonely nights. Karlach suffers a permanent -4 to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Constitution"&gt;Constitution&lt;/LSTag&gt;, -2 to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Strength"&gt;Strength&lt;/LSTag&gt;, -2 to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Wisdom"&gt;Wisdom&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and -2 to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Intelligence"&gt;Intelligence&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content> 
	<content contentuid="h5bf8c986g5cf8g4c23gbf61g35188585e078" version="1">Soul Branding: Karlach</content> 
	<content contentuid="hd712ad9fg798cg43f0g92f8g288f2e72f692" version="1">You have marked Karlach as a concubine of Grazzt, stealing her strength. The inferno that once raged is now but a comforting heat on lonely nights. You receive +2 to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Constitution"&gt;Constitution&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and +1 to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Strength"&gt;Strength&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content> 

	<content contentuid="h2c2c4b95gcb0eg472agaee8g4d31ec822da9" version="1">As the brand burns upon Shadowheart's soul, power courses through you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Lust. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Around you swirls the darkness of Shadowheart's mind, an ocean of shadow, dotted with the brief, bright lights of her few memories.  There is so much here, so much contained in those lights and scattered in half-formed waves across the rest of her mind.  And then the brand begins to pull it all away. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; The ocean brightens, even as the pinprick stars dull and lose their luster. Memories she will never miss are lost forever, and alongside them her pain, her brilliance, her determination, her devotion. All washed away in a new tide, swept away to make room for pleasant bliss and eager submission. Your own mind takes much of what is lost, and you relish in the sensation, as Shadowheart lets out a distant giggle.</content>
 	<content contentuid="hbcfa9185gf833g4458gb3e8gbbb8574dfa78" version="1">Soul Branded: Shadowheart</content> 
	<content contentuid="hd07f7cebg048cg45a0gb470g4ffd3168ce46" version="1">Shadowheart has been marked as a concubine of Grazzt.  Her mind has been dulled and her body ripened, changing the cleric into a form suited to new kinds of worship.  Shadowheart suffers a permanent -4 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Wisdom"&gt;Wisdom&lt;/LSTag&gt;, -2 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Intelligence"&gt;Intelligence&lt;/LSTag&gt;, -2 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Dexterity"&gt;Dexterity&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and -2 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Charisma"&gt;Charisma&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content> 
	<content contentuid="hc1439db6g36d4g40d0g8fc3gd5e1b7fffa61" version="1">Soul Branding: Shadowheart</content> 
	<content contentuid="h68b9929eg3522g41b0gaaa3g8b7a5c8aa958" version="1">You have marked Shadowheart as a concubine of Grazzt, stealing her wisdom and determination. The agile mind that once scrutinized the world is now subdued, content, and tamed. You receive +2 to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Wisdom"&gt;Wisdom&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and +1 to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Charisma"&gt;Charisma&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content> 

	<content contentuid="h2179b880g8f1eg4e4eg8537g35da4baa3df9" version="1">As the brand burns upon Minthara's soul, power courses through you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Lust. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Minthara's intellect has always been her weapon, piercing through riddles, strategems, and divine secrets alike. Now, with the surge of the soul brand, it begins to ebb away. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Your own mind sharpens, reveling in the whispers of lost secrets and tactics that had once been guarded inside her intelligent mind. The feeling is intoxicating, like tasting a flavor you've never encountered before. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Simultaneously, you witness the transformation of Minthara. The spark of her intimidating intellect fades into sweet innocence. Her body, once a fierce vessel of a paladin, morphs into a softer, more docile form. She's now more accommodating, pliable to your commands. </content>
 	<content contentuid="h81c44f89g3f4dg42ddgb81cgf773d776ba15" version="1">Soul Branded: Minthara</content> 
	<content contentuid="h13c56017g3752g4d43gbf24gaa75dd17144a" version="1">Minthara has been marked as a concubine of Grazzt. Her formidable intellect has been noticeably diminished, reshaping her into a vessel compliant to her new tasks. Minthara suffers a permanent -4 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Intelligence"&gt;Intelligence&lt;/LSTag&gt;, -2 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Wisdom"&gt;Wisdom&lt;/LSTag&gt;, -2 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Charisma"&gt;Charisma&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and -2 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Constitution"&gt;Constitution&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content> 
	<content contentuid="h3b4e1b76gfcd2g40abg8b61gef6146796877" version="1">Soul Branding: Minthara</content> 
	<content contentuid="hd8533d7cg9e64g4c39g9c62gd86b3de2b634" version="1">You have marked Minthara as a concubine of Grazzt, stealing her intelligence and cunning. The cruel mind that once manipulated others is barely fit for that task now. You receive +2 to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Intelligence"&gt;Intelligence&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and +1 to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Wisdom"&gt;Wisdom&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content> 

	<content contentuid="hf0ec2efdgb7aag4672g821fgc73c733c6fb8" version="1">As the brand sears onto Aylin's soul, another rush of power surges into you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Lust. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; The fierce Dame Aylin shudders and moans at your feet, helplessly groping herself as her silver glow dulls and fades. The brand drinks deeply of her divine nature, stripping her of the gifts that Selune gave her, and forcing her to writhe in bliss as it begins to glow instead. You feel it pouring into you through the connection, the presence and charisma of a demigod suffusing your every action as she becomes more and more lost in the fog of her own desires. As you lift your hand to examine the beautiful sheen that your skin has gained, you wonder what other uses you might be able to find for the famous Nightsong now that she's yours. You wonder if you might need to claim Isobel from her as well...</content>
 	<content contentuid="h5421b20fgd533g495eg8e74g0775ed8ffe25" version="1">Soul Branded: Nightsong</content> 
	<content contentuid="h38fe1a18g109ag42abgb5e9g0507dc07a513" version="1">Aylin, the once-daughter of Selune, now bears the brand of Graz'zt, denoting her as his concubine. While her divine grace and strength have been forfeited, her altered state glows with a softer allure and divine elegance, signaling her transformation for a gentler role. Aylin suffers a permanent -4 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Charisma"&gt;Charisma&lt;/LSTag&gt;, -2 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Wisdom"&gt;Wisdom&lt;/LSTag&gt;, -2 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Constitution"&gt;Constitution&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and -2 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Strength"&gt;Strength&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content> 
	<content contentuid="h952fb843ge90dg4569g9e47g47f60341461f" version="1">Soul Branding: Nightsong</content> 
	<content contentuid="h12666615g2691g48f8g94cagda05af43e664" version="1">You have marked Dame Aylin as a concubine of Grazzt, stealing her charisma and divine grace. You receive +2 to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Charisma"&gt;Charisma&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and +1 to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Constitution"&gt;Constitution&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content> 

	<content contentuid="h8f831e2dg5ae0g4c73g870dg720e0c883654" version="1">As the brand burns upon Lae'zel's soul, power courses through you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Lust. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; The power and skill of a githyanki warrior, the history of training at Creche K'liir, passes from her pleasure-soaked brain and into yours. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; You feel her mastery of body and mind, the unbreakable determination that fills her become yours, and her knowledge of weapon arts and war-training are stolen forever.  In those same moments, the brand is changing Lae'zel.  The hard edges of her body melt away before your eyes, her fit fighting body softening into gorgeous curves more suitable for the new concubine.  As the gith grunts through her climax, you watch the cold fury and arrogance that once defined her ebbing away in the tide of pleasure, leaving a glassy eyed gith more suited to laying eggs than fighting. </content>
 	<content contentuid="h64305a98gad79g4f38g9947g1b6e158e8e98" version="1">Soul Branded: Lae'zel</content> 
	<content contentuid="h11ea562dg0c4cg4346gbb73g2b8b8fd2e1d2" version="1">Lae'zel has been marked as a concubine of Grazzt.  Her power and skill have been stolen, and her hard edges smoothed over with supple curves and dull bliss. Lae'zel suffers a permanent -4 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Strength"&gt;Strength&lt;/LSTag&gt;, -2 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Constitution"&gt;Constitution&lt;/LSTag&gt;, -2 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Dexterity"&gt;Dexterity&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and -2 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Intelligence"&gt;Intelligence&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content> 
	<content contentuid="h05e66b1agdb10g4f7cgb004g94ad2dae8f7c" version="1">Soul Branding: Lae'zel</content> 
	<content contentuid="h6b9c379fg315dg451fg8d66g91cf5fdac70a" version="1">You have marked Lae'zel as a concubine of Grazzt, stealing her strength and deftness. You receive +2 to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Strength"&gt;Strength&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and +1 to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Dexterity"&gt;Dexterity&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content> 

	<content contentuid="h341a9687gae81g4992gaeefg14f3d394b6ea" version="1">Profane Succor: Taste of Darkness</content> 
	<content contentuid="h48e121d6g6cb0g4d3cg953dg0ddcd17d2b10" version="1">Your dealing in the dark art of soul branding has borne fruit - you move with supernatural speed and have outstanding vigor. You receive a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="MovementSpeed"&gt;movement speed&lt;/LSTag&gt; bonus of [1] and your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="HitPoints"&gt;Hit Points&lt;/LSTag&gt; maximum is increased by [2].</content> 
	<content contentuid="hf770a724g35c2g4896gbaf7gab8fb07dddc2" version="1">Profane Succor: Twilight Infusion</content> 
	<content contentuid="h6e7eaa0cgc1a6g4724gbf99g101c4e920e1d" version="1">Your continued indulgence in soul branding has invigorated your body, letting you move with unnatural alacrity. You receive an additional &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="BonusActionPoint"&gt;bonus action&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content> 
	<content contentuid="h934010a0ge945g4d26gb6aag0d420b6b06a9" version="1">Profane Succor: Abyssal Embrace</content> 
	<content contentuid="h60b7231cg993dg4940g9b8fgd5d98d2f3855" version="1">Your mastery of soul branding has reformed your body, giving you legendary speed and reactions. You receive an additional &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="ActionPoint"&gt;action&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="ReactionActionPoint"&gt;reaction&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content> 

	<content contentuid="h5f1ee53cg1e92g4122g9c77g8153bbb4641e" version="1">You wake from a fitful dream in which Graz'zt came to visit your camp and indulged in the carnal pleasures of your body, hidden from the eyes and ears of your companions. However, by the rivulet running down your legs and your throbbing cunt, you are not entirely sure if it was just a dream. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not long before you notice a new tugging sensation on your chest. Looking down, you see sinister looking chains connecting the piercings He has branded you with. You smile as you know that this must be Graz'zt showing you greater favor, likely due to your diligent practice of Soul Branding, collecting concubines for Him while also taking some power for yourself. </content> 
</contentList>