<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><contentList>
	<content contentuid="hfaa9495bgf4b2g4e9egb8a4g76ce3114f1e2" version="1">Graz'zt's Box of Pleasure</content>
	<content contentuid="hbd7dbcfage396g4a04gaf80g0e1cbef1b923" version="1">An exquisite box that when held close whispers in your ears of pleasures unimaginable within. Dare you indulge yourself?</content>


	<content contentuid="h006cdbccgb99dg41dag88c8gaa169f365660" version="1">Ring of Graz'zt</content>
	<content contentuid="hf332a893gb7e5g48e8ga172gb1350ba26258" version="1">This exquisite ring boasts multiple faceted edges. Surprisingly, wearing such a sharp design, instead of inducing discomfort, evokes a sense of captivating pleasure.</content>

	<content contentuid="hb53111fdg2a06g4db0ga18ag955f373b88ea" version="1">Rings of Graz'zt</content>
	<content contentuid="h1a8869deg6af7g4288gabb6g51a44e4dac4f" version="1">Warped under the Dark Prince's influence and your submission to pleasure, the once benign ring shifted from your finger to embed itself into your nipples. Forged from the Abyss's darkest materials, they bear intricate markings, a phantom echo of a dread promise inscribed by Graz'zt himself. Wearing these rings is not simply an accessorizing choice, but a profound declaration of submission to Graz'zt's will. They look very painful to remove.</content>

	<content contentuid="hf2880447g4608g455fg8f53gb17e9f991973" version="1">Chains of Graz'zt</content>
	<content contentuid="h650c93fbg1a38g416dg9c78g55040bd051c8" version="1">Warped under the Dark Prince's influence and your submission to pleasure, the once benign ring shifted from your finger to embed itself into your nipples. Forged from the Abyss's darkest materials, they bear intricate markings, a phantom echo of a dread promise inscribed by Graz'zt himself. Chains bind them together, each link carrying the weight of your depravity. Wearing these signals your profound dedication to the Dark Prince himself..</content>

	<content contentuid="hde2acefage3dfg4bb7g9be1g168e5a850419" version="1">Chains of Submission</content>
	<content contentuid="hd8054508gd245g4f57ga37fgd0b797b5f41f" version="1">Warped further by the Dark Prince's influence and your unabashed surrender to pleasure, the Chains of Graz'zt transformed yet again. Adapting to your deepening depravity, a third piercing emerges to mark your most intimate area, binding it by chain to the existing links. Crafted from the Abyss's darkest materials, each piece bears intricate markings. It is a tangible symbol of your hedonistic ascension. Transcending beyond Graz'zt, it marks your dedication to the concept of Submission itself. </content>


	<content contentuid="hc9532287gc215g4b64gb0b9gdcf1c6b88168" version="1">Hide Piercings</content>
	<content contentuid="h1d34609fg9056g40f0g8b16g75d78b3f0719" version="1">Project a deceptive illusion to conceal the piercings. Although they remain unseen by others, the sensation of their existence is accentuated with every gesture you make.</content>

	<content contentuid="h141bfe18g45c2g41adga510gb4940086a823" version="1">Stop Hiding Piercings</content>
	<content contentuid="h8663aa4ag1880g401fg8dfegedccb4cfbab7" version="1">Unveil the piercings, allowing others to see the source of your squirming.</content>

	<content contentuid="hd8b60198g3295g4492g8c2bg6573aa4d468c" version="1">Hide Lust Brand</content>
	<content contentuid="hf6bbaac1g667fg4ed8g9991gf530b010e6cc" version="1">Suppress your lust brand from showing. While it remains hidden to others, their influence is felt by how it twists any innocent thoughts into indulgent ones.</content>

	<content contentuid="hf59a353ag7163g4c58g9a71gc292983f66df" version="1">Stop Hiding Lust Brand</content>
	<content contentuid="h55831fcege9d0g417ega07fga644c2be1514" version="1">Unveil your Lust Brand, displaying your lustful nature.</content>


	<content contentuid="hbcb5e2e9g3071g45ccg9c2ag542923c2bfb5" version="1">Dark Inspection</content>
	<content contentuid="h8f9aedb4gc403g4826g85f6g1464f6ffae21" version="1">You channel your new profane powers to peer into someone's dark history.</content>


	<content contentuid="hd7a5e852g115fg4acag9d5cg434b0db1cf45" version="1">Touch of Graz'zt</content>
	<content contentuid="h0d74cf45g725dg491fgad60g66d042395078" version="1">Caress of Graz'zt</content>
	<content contentuid="h80a730ddg41f6g4c3eg9de5gaac90824d9e7" version="1">Embrace of Graz'zt</content>
	<content contentuid="h78ae2f4bg1e76g4211g81d4gc2868ea95615" version="1">Surrender yourself to spectral caresses, letting ethereal hands explore your body. You gain [1] + &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityModifier"&gt;Charisma Modifier&lt;/LSTag&gt; and receive [2] &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="LI_PLEASURE"&gt;Pleasure&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>

	<content contentuid="hf788275agceb2g4d5fga7a4g420bf51538a6" version="1">Lust Brand</content> 
	<content contentuid="h8142038fg3a37g4debga007g8a0224322227" version="1">Imbued with dark potency, this indelible mark stirs unnatural desire in any that gaze upon it. Skillfully etched into your womb, the Lust Brand is a constant reminder that you are undeniably a creature of pure, untempered lust. It impairs your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Wisdom"&gt;Wisdom&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Intelligence"&gt;Intelligence&lt;/LSTag&gt; by [1] while boosting your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Charisma"&gt;Charisma&lt;/LSTag&gt; by the same amount.</content>  

	<content contentuid="hc65a1066gd4dcg4c8fga47cg0663c71c35a9" version="1">Ecstatic Lash</content>
	<content contentuid="hc806e45dg9782g457fg9458g139fbfeb3ce0" version="2">Concentrate your hedonistic thoughts into an ethereal whip, striking at the minds of your foes. You inflict [3] + &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityModifier"&gt;Charisma Modifier&lt;/LSTag&gt; &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="LI_PLEASURE"&gt;Pleasure&lt;/LSTag&gt;; if they are in &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="LI_BLISS"&gt;Bliss&lt;/LSTag&gt;, their mind is overwhelmed and they suffer damage. Otherwise, they gain [2] and move [1] towards you, seeking the source of their pleasure.</content>

	<content contentuid="h168d0c0dg168cg47f0g8bffg96a6dad6bca4" version="1">Lustful High</content>
	<content contentuid="h12913d1ag170eg4c7cg9702g98261303a6a1" version="2">Your arousal distracts you from pain, letting you endure more than usual and providing you [1].</content>


	<content contentuid="h21177641gd1cdg4273g8986g9addca845dcf" version="1">After a breathlessly wet dream, you wake to find the Ring of Graz'zt gone from your finger. You panic until you feel a slightly painful burning in your chest, and you realize the ring has split in two and embedded itself in your nipples. Graz'zt has claimed you in your sleep, and you are His.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each transformed ring bears a sinister black sheen, its surface eerily smooth against your skin. Spiked adornments, reminiscent of thorns on a rose stem, trace along its length, hinting at a painful removal. His claim is not easily relinquished. </content> 
	<content contentuid="h2d77b445ga917g493cga3b1g3e2c07e01b14" version="1">After succumbing to pleasure again, you realize with a start that something is off this time. Usually, the pleasure builds to a peak then ebbs, but the wave you're currently riding on seems to continue to build. Your hands follow that feeling, almost of their own accord, but stop a few inches short: there's a heat, a throbbing warmth that wasn't there before. You glance down and your breath catches. A mark, a brand- His brand! now claims your pubic mound, glowing with a pink light that pulses in time with your breath. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As your hands begin downward once more and your eyes close, the last thing you see before succumbing to pleasure is the brand's glow, beating in time with your ragged, hungry breaths.</content> 
	<content contentuid="h685322a8gf4e4g42b2g8adeg01a6838bd05a" version="1">You feel a sinister gaze in your sleep. Fortunately for you, or unfortunately, Graz'zt seems to already have his eyes set on another in your party. He spares you only a glance, and the rest of your dream is a sweet and incoherent mess. (remove the ring when sleeping to avoid this message)</content> 

	<content contentuid="hb3436a69g5fe9g47d8g8bdcg1f6c577d38a5" version="1">, Consort of Graz'zt</content> 

	<content contentuid="h4eb20687g805cg44e2gbd44g0f27a1396731" version="1">Abyssal Inheritance: Soul Branding</content> 
	<content contentuid="h77039ab3g086fg4419g874cgada38d554dc1" version="1">Through experience, you have come to better understand how to give others Bliss. This is when they are most vulernable, and something urges you to leave your mark on them, devouring their potential for your own.</content>  

	<content contentuid="hfba2dee3g02a6g4324gbd9bgdca9e9642f7d" version="1">Soul Brand</content> 
	<content contentuid="he8567035g78b1g4c1bgbe03ga35dc08ae331" version="1">You exploit someone's vulnerability when in &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="LI_BLISS"&gt;Bliss&lt;/LSTag&gt; to permanently mark their soul, devouring their potential for your own. Their resistance will get weaker the more they are overloaded by Bliss.</content>  

	<content contentuid="h9bf02c9bgf7ddg44ceg8e1eg023f96d55bd5" version="1">Soul Branding Fatigue</content> 
	<content contentuid="hc8831433g9237g4fe3g8701g3fe378a8e671" version="1">Soul branding is not to be done lightly. You are exhausted, body and soul, from attempting to do so. You suffer -1 to Charisma and Constitution per stack. You lose 1 stack per turn.</content>  

	<content contentuid="haecf5a8cg9f44g4169g861fgcebc4b56e2d9" version="1">Power consuming</content> 
	<content contentuid="h322a959egaf76g4f72gbc10g8d52412babcc" version="1">The newly formed soul brand is transferring power from the target to you.</content>  
	<content contentuid="h7336905dgccc5g4e6bgac44ge03766a7385e" version="1">Power draining</content> 
	<content contentuid="h53b9b7acgea92g4df1g915cg628572698478" version="1">Your power is being quickly drained away.</content>  

</contentList>